Fortnite is not just cartoon PUBG,
there are huge differences.
For example, you can build stuff.
And, while Fortnite was developed by a company that also makes a game engine,
PUBG makes your computer sound like an engine.
As I was downloading it, which took about 3 minutes,
(tough luck Australia) I decided this was the game
I was gonna give my life to.
To become an expert... Then I came in second place in my first match
by hiding in bushes.
Really need to be able to cut these down.
I should be celebrating my placement, but I feel hollow.
I'm just too naturally talented at this.
I feel bad for taking the award away from someone
who deserved it, and didn't
hide in bushes like a camping asshole.
Now, every match I play will just
make me feel dead inside... Like I do in real life.
I have to find a way to win, but at the same
time let someone else win.
What if I reach second place again, and then take suicide? I wouldn't win, but I knew I could have.
No, there has to be another way.
That's when I saw it, there's a hole in the sky!
If I can get up there, I can jump over the storm.
Hmm... can't build a tower.
In the Bible, they built one and God invented languages so they couldn't communicate.
What if I build a tower here
and the developers remove the chat feature?
I'm instead going to have to build... a stairway to heaven.
Yeah... that's... yeah, I knew it.
What I meant to say was, a
staircase to the celestial sphere. The first try,
I felt confident. I landed on a mountain, so I was
closer to the sky. Things went great...
Then I fell to the ground and died. I didn't have enough
material. Math is not my strongest
subject. I need to spend more time gathering wood
in a place with a lot of it. This
song does not end.
There. 40 stairs should be enough to reach space.
I'm really making progress! And I
forgot about the battle royale part.
This game really needs a construction underway sign
so people can build in peace.
OK... I need to travel far away from the bus to avoid
the whole online thing. In this swamp, no one will be able to find me.
But flying this far away has given me
less time to finish my construction.
If I rush... I failed hard. Maybe I can
build through the stor... Nope, it ripped my staircases to pieces.
Not to worry, the water will slow my fall.
That's some hard water!
This time I will finally succeed, I mean, look at his hair!
And, I almost reached it.
But then my character froze to death because it's cold up there.
Now you might say,
"Go to the store and buy a jacket!"
But they didn't have one on sale.
And even if they did, it wouldn't have mattered
because my character would have died from no oxygen
I'm sure I probably could have solved that too
but you know what, instead
I'm gonna go do the DRUGS.
That promising teenager died from an overdose
ten minutes later. Hello, I'm Kilian.
Yes, this entire thing was an anti-drug PSA.
What led Battlemaster2005
down this path?
"I feel bad for taking the award away
from someone who deserved it." Exactly! He didn't
try his best, because he considered people online
to be human. Having empathy for other
players? What a loser! So always try your best
in a video game, or you will be
sucking dick for heroin.